[Music]
the year has moved along with surprising
speed It Feels Like Only Yesterday I was
watching the bees hunting for morels in
the thickets and Gathering the first of
the rhubarb Harvest now we are well on
our way towards fall and I expect soon
enough the rains will come in the cool
fog and I will be out my old woin and
packing away my linen
dresses however I am still enjoying the
last months of warmth eating copious
amounts of ice cream reading voraciously
and bringing my baby Outdoors as much as
possible to soak up the beauty
[Music]
unfortunately we've had a lot of smoky
Skies due to wildfires so every moment
the air quality is good enough to be
outdoors has been a gift but I admit I'm
looking forward to the Autumn it will be
a much needed cooling balm on this fire
prone Valley
[Music]
contrary to the Past I'm rarely alone
these days baby is always here my family
is often visiting and helping around the
house our home is full of laughter and
music and Company indeed choosing a
simple and slow life comes in so many
beautiful forms
[Music]
my fairy child is rambunctious and ready
to discover the world so we spend the
early mornings giggling and pretending
we sprouted wings and are flying through
the air climbing mountains made of
pillows and imagining all the future
Adventures we will go on together it's
exhausting in the best way little things
I used to take for granted like taking a
shower or brushing my hair have become
treasured gifts that I enjoy so much
more now small Joys are highlighted in
this new world of mine nothing is done
without gratitude
[Music]
I still get time to myself when I need
it thank goodness however things are not
the same but I didn't want them to be I
think we can view change as something
negative when it doesn't go as smoothly
as we expected it to or we struggle to
find our peace but I've rather enjoyed
blundering through this new chapter of
my story throughout my life I felt
lonely at times other times simply
happily alone
living with family in an apartment
Living Single in a cottage then with my
husband seeing my mother and father
retire and move into a quiet little
cabin and my Abita planning to move in
with them has reminded me that our
living situations often change whether
we wish them to or not in all honesty
Parenthood has brought fears to the
surface all the medical bills car
repairs and unexpected costs have been
anxiety provoking we've had to stay
centered through it all and lean on each
other for support remembering that
slowly we will figure things out but
it's hard to not let practical fears
take hold I still Fear the Future at
times and I don't have answers or
solutions for that sometimes I just need
to feel it the anxiety the unknown and
accept that this too is part of growing
just feeling and knowing that that's
okay
[Music]
to live a simple quiet life has no rules
or standards there is no right or wrong
way I don't think we should have
expectations instead to live each day
intentionally nurse and inner peace
connect with ourselves and remember to
breathe and that's the best I can do
right now
[Music]
is
such
a my husband was kind enough to put this
rocking chair on this porch for me
because he knows I've been cooped up a
little bit at home lately for
understandable reasons and I probably
will be staying for the most part at
home for the next couple months we've
been able to sit here in the mornings
and watch the sunrise before the sun
gets too bright and enjoy all the
flowers and the Ambiance of the summer
well I think I will be rocking on this
chair for quite a while longer because
this one is taking a nap so we will be
here a while and we will spend some time
investigating the garden and seeing how
everything is growing once he wakes up a
little bit more
[Music]